{
    "cards": [    
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Under the shared responsibility model, which of the following is the customer responsible for?",
                "choices": [
                    "Ensuring that disk drives are wiped after use.",
                    "Ensuring that firmware is updated on hardware devices.",
                    "Ensuring that data is encrypted at rest.",
                    "Ensuring that network cables are category six or higher."
                ],
                "answer": "Ensuring that data is encrypted at rest."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "The use of what AWS feature or service allows companies to track and categorize spending on a detailed level?",
                "choices": [
                    "Cost allocation tags",
                    "Consolidated billing",
                    "AWS Budgets",
                    "AWS Marketplace"
                ],
                "answer": "Cost allocation tags"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which service stores objects, provides real-time access to those objects, and offers versioning and lifecycle capabilities?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Glacier",
                    "AWS Storage Gateway",
                    "Amazon S3",
                    "Amazon EBS"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon S3"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What AWS team assists customers with accelerating cloud adoption through paid engagements in any of several specialty practice areas?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Enterprise Support",
                    "AWS Solutions Architects",
                    "AWS Professional Services",
                    "AWS Account Managers"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Professional Services"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A customer would like to design and build a new workload on AWS Cloud but does not have the AWS-related software technical expertise in-house. Which of the following AWS programs can a customer take advantage of to achieve that outcome?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Partner Network Technology Partners",
                    "AWS Marketplace",
                    "AWS Partner Network Consulting Partners",
                    "AWS Service Catalog"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Partner Network Consulting Partners"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Distributing workloads across multiple Availability Zones supports which cloud architecture design principle?",
                "choices": [
                    "Implement automation.",
                    "Design for agility.",
                    "Design for failure.",
                    "Implement elasticity."
                ],
                "answer": "Design for failure."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services can host a Microsoft SQL Server database? ",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon EC2",
                    "Amazon Aurora",
                    "Amazon Redshift",
                    "Amazon S3"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon EC2"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services can host a Microsoft SQL Server database?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)",
                    "Amazon Aurora",
                    "Amazon S3",
                    "Amazon Redshift"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following inspects AWS environments to find opportunities that can save money for users and also improve system performance?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Cost Explorer",
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor",
                    "Consolidated billing",
                    "Detailed billing"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Trusted Advisor"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following Amazon EC2 pricing models allow customers to use existing server-bound software licenses?",
                "choices": [
                    "Spot Instances",
                    "Reserved Instances",
                    "Dedicated Hosts",
                    "On-Demand Instances"
                ],
                "answer": "Dedicated Hosts"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS characteristics make AWS cost effective for a workload with dynamic user demand?",
                "choices": [
                    "High availability",
                    "Shared security model",
                    "Elasticity",
                    "Reliability"
                ],
                "answer": "Elasticity"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS characteristics make AWS cost effective for a workload with dynamic user demand?",
                "choices": [
                    "High availability",
                    "Shared security model",
                    "Pay-as-you-go pricing",
                    "Reliability"
                ],
                "answer": "Pay-as-you-go pricing"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which service enables risk auditing by continuously monitoring and logging account activity, including user actions in the AWS Management Console and AWS SDKs?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon CloudWatch",
                    "AWS CloudTrail",
                    "AWS Config",
                    "AWS Health"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS CloudTrail"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are characteristics of Amazon S3?",
                "choices": [
                    "A durable storage system",
                    "A local file store",
                    "A network file system",
                    "A durable storage system"
                ],
                "answer": "A durable storage system"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are characteristics of Amazon S3?",
                "choices": [
                    "An object store",
                    "A local file store",
                    "A network file system",
                    "A durable storage system"
                ],
                "answer": "An object store"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which services can be used across hybrid AWS Cloud architectures? ",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Route 53",
                    "Virtual Private Gateway",
                    "Classic Load Balancer",
                    "Auto Scaling"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Route 53"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which services can be used across hybrid AWS Cloud architectures? ",
                "choices": [
                    "Virtual Private Gateway",
                    "Virtual Private Gateway",
                    "Classic Load Balancer",
                    "Auto Scaling"
                ],
                "answer": "Virtual Private Gateway"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What costs are included when comparing AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) with on-premises TCO?",
                "choices": [
                    "Project management",
                    "Antivirus software licensing",
                    "Data center security",
                    "Software development"
                ],
                "answer": "Data center security"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A company is considering using AWS for a self-hosted database that requires a nightly shutdown for maintenance and cost-saving purposes. Which service should the company use?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Redshift",
                    "Amazon DynamoDB",
                    "Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) with Amazon EC2 instance store",
                    "Amazon EC2 with Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon EC2 with Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is a correct relationship between regions, Availability Zones, and edge locations?",
                "choices": [
                    "Data centers contain regions.",
                    "Regions contain Availability Zones.",
                    "Availability Zones contain edge locations.",
                    "Edge locations contain regions."
                ],
                "answer": "Regions contain Availability Zones."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS tools assist with estimating costs?",
                "choices": [
                    "Detailed billing report",
                    "Cost Estimator",
                    "Cost allocation tags",
                    "AWS Estimator"
                ],
                "answer": "Cost allocation tags"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS tools assist with estimating costs?",
                "choices": [
                    "Detailed billing report",
                    "Cost Estimator",
                    "AWS Simple Monthly Calculator",
                    "AWS Estimator"
                ],
                "answer": " AWS Simple Monthly Calculator"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are advantages of AWS consolidated billing?",
                "choices": [
                    "The ability to receive one bill for multiple accounts",
                    "Service limits increasing by default in all accounts",
                    "A fixed discount on the monthly bill",
                    "The automatic extension of the master account's AWS support plan to all accounts"
                ],
                "answer": "The ability to receive one bill for multiple accounts"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are advantages of AWS consolidated billing?",
                "choices": [
                    "Potential volume discounts, as usage in all accounts is combined",
                    "Service limits increasing by default in all accounts",
                    "A fixed discount on the monthly bill",
                    "The automatic extension of the master account's AWS support plan to all accounts"
                ],
                "answer": "Potential volume discounts, as usage in all accounts is combined"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following Reserved Instance (RI) pricing models provides the highest average savings compared to On-Demand pricing?",
                "choices": [
                    "One-year, No Upfront, Standard RI pricing",
                    "One-year, All Upfront, Convertible RI pricing",
                    "Three-year, All Upfront, Standard RI pricing",
                    "Three-year, No Upfront, Convertible RI pricing"
                ],
                "answer": "Three-year, All Upfront, Standard RI pricing"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Compared with costs in traditional and virtualized data centers, AWS has:",
                "choices": [
                    "greater variable costs and greater upfront costs.",
                    "fixed usage costs and lower upfront costs.",
                    "lower variable costs and greater upfront costs.",
                    "lower variable costs and lower upfront costs."
                ],
                "answer": "lower variable costs and lower upfront costs."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A characteristic of edge locations is that they:",
                "choices": [
                    "host Amazon EC2 instances closer to users.",
                    "help lower latency and improve performance for users.",
                    "cache frequently changing data without reaching the origin server.",
                    "refresh data changes daily."
                ],
                "answer": "help lower latency and improve performance for users."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following can limit Amazon Storage Service (Amazon S3) bucket access to specific users?",
                "choices": [
                    "A public and private key-pair",
                    "Amazon Inspector",
                    "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) policies",
                    "Security Groups"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) policies"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following security-related actions are available at no cost?",
                "choices": [
                    "Calling AWS Support",
                    "Contacting AWS Professional Services to request a workshop",
                    "Accessing forums, blogs, and whitepapers",
                    "Attending AWS classes at a local university"
                ],
                "answer": "Accessing forums, blogs, and whitepapers"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the Reserved Instance (RI) pricing models can change the attributes of the RI as long as the exchange results in the creation of RIs of equal or greater value?",
                "choices": [
                    "Dedicated RIs",
                    "Scheduled RIs",
                    "Convertible RIs",
                    "Standard RIs"
                ],
                "answer": "Convertible RIs"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS feature will reduce the customer's total cost of ownership (TCO)?",
                "choices": [
                    "Shared responsibility security model",
                    "Single tenancy",
                    "Elastic computing",
                    "Encryption"
                ],
                "answer": "Elastic computing"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following services will automatically scale with an expected increase in web traffic?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS CodePipeline",
                    "Elastic Load Balancing",
                    "Amazon EBS",
                    "AWS Direct Connect"
                ],
                "answer": "Elastic Load Balancing"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS tools assist with estimating costs?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS CodePipeline",
                    "Elastic Load Balancing",
                    "Amazon EBS",
                    "AWS Direct Connect"
                ],
                "answer": "Elastic Load Balancing"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Where are AWS compliance documents, such as an SOC 1 report, located?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Inspector",
                    "AWS CloudTrail",
                    "AWS Artifact",
                    "AWS Certificate Manager"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Artifact"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Under the AWS shared responsibility model, which of the following activities are the customer's responsibility?",
                "choices": [
                    "Patching operating system components for Amazon Relational Database Server (Amazon RDS)",
                    "Encrypting data on the client-side",
                    "Training the data center staff",
                    "Maintaining environmental controls within a data center"
                ],
                "answer": "Encrypting data on the client-side"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Under the AWS shared responsibility model, which of the following activities are the customer's responsibility?",
                "choices": [
                    "Patching operating system components for Amazon Relational Database Server (Amazon RDS)",
                    "Configuring Network Access Control Lists (ACL)",
                    "Training the data center staff",
                    "Maintaining environmental controls within a data center"
                ],
                "answer": "Configuring Network Access Control Lists (ACL)"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which is a recommended pattern for designing a highly available architecture on AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "Ensure that components have low-latency network connectivity.",
                    "Run enough Amazon EC2 instances to operate at peak load.",
                    "Ensure that the application is designed to accommodate failure of any single component.",
                    "Use a monolithic application that handles all operations."
                ],
                "answer": "Ensure that the application is designed to accommodate failure of any single component."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "According to best practices, how should an application be designed to run in the AWS Cloud?",
                "choices": [
                    "Use tighly coupled components.",
                    "Use loosely coupled components.",
                    "Use infrequently coupled components.",
                    "Use frequently coupled components."
                ],
                "answer": "Use loosely coupled components."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "AWS supports which of the following methods to add security to Identity and Access Management (IAM) users?",
                "choices": [
                    "Implementing Amazon Recognition",
                    "Using AWS Shield-protected resources",
                    "Blocking access with Security Groups",
                    "Using Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)"
                ],
                "answer": "Using Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "AWS supports which of the following methods to add security to Identity and Access Management (IAM) users?",
                "choices": [
                    "Implementing Amazon Recognition",
                    "Using AWS Shield-protected resources",
                    "Blocking access with Security Groups",
                    "Enforcing password strength and expiration"
                ],
                "answer": "Enforcing password strength and expiration"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services should be used for read/write of constantly changing data?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Glacier",
                    "Amazon RDS",
                    "AWS Snowball",
                    "Amazon Redshift"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon RDS"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services should be used for read/write of constantly changing data?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Glacier",
                    "Amazon EFS",
                    "AWS Snowball",
                    "Amazon Redshift"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon EFS"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What is one of the advantages of the Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)?",
                "choices": [
                    "It simplifies relational database administration tasks.",
                    "It provides 99.99999999999% reliability and durability.",
                    "It automatically scales databases for loads.",
                    "It enabled users to dynamically adjust CPU and RAM resources."
                ],
                "answer": "It simplifies relational database administration tasks."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A customer needs to run a MySQL database that easily scales. Which AWS service should they use?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Aurora",
                    "Amazon Redshift",
                    "Amazon DynamoDB",
                    "Amazon ElastiCache"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Aurora"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following components of the AWS Global Infrastructure consists of one or more discrete data centers interconnected through low latency links?",
                "choices": [
                    "Availability Zone",
                    "Edge location",
                    "Region",
                    "Private networking"
                ],
                "answer": "Availability Zone"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is a shared control between the customer and AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "Providing a key for Amazon S3 client-side encryption",
                    "Configuration of an Amazon EC2 instance",
                    "Environmental controls of physical AWS data centers",
                    "Awareness and training"
                ],
                "answer": "Awareness and training"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "How many Availability Zones should compute resources be provisioned across to achieve high availability?",
                "choices": [
                    "A minimum of one",
                    "A minimum of two",
                    "A minimum of three",
                    "A minimum of four or more"
                ],
                "answer": "A minimum of two"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "One of the advantages to moving infrastructure from an on-premises data center to the AWS Cloud is:",
                "choices": [
                    "it allows the business to eliminate IT bills.",
                    "it allows the business to put a server in each customer's data center.",
                    "it allows the business to focus on business activities.",
                    "it allows the business to leave servers unpatched."
                ],
                "answer": "it allows the business to focus on business activities."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What is the lowest-cost, durable storage option for retaining database backups for immediate retrieval?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon S3",
                    "Amazon Glacier",
                    "Amazon EBS",
                    "Amazon EC2 Instance Store"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon S3"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS IAM feature allows developers to access AWS services through the AWS CLI?",
                "choices": [
                    "API keys",
                    "Access keys",
                    "User names/Passwords",
                    "SSH keys"
                ],
                "answer": "Access keys"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is a fast and reliable NoSQL database service?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Redshift",
                    "Amazon RDS",
                    "Amazon DynamoDB",
                    "Amazon S3"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon DynamoDB"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What is an example of agility in the AWS Cloud?",
                "choices": [
                    "Access to multiple instance types",
                    "Access to managed services",
                    "Using Consolidated Billing to produce one bill",
                    "Decreased acquisition time for new compute resources"
                ],
                "answer": "Decreased acquisition time for new compute resources"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which service should a customer use to consolidate and centrally manage multiple AWS accounts?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS IAM",
                    "AWS Organizations",
                    "AWS Schema Conversion Tool",
                    "AWS Config"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Organizations"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What approach to transcoding a large number of individual video files adheres to AWS architecture principles?",
                "choices": [
                    "Using many instances in parallel",
                    "Using a single large instance during off-peak hours",
                    "Using dedicated hardware",
                    "Using a large GPU instance type"
                ],
                "answer": "Using many instances in parallel"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "For which auditing process does AWS have sole responsibility?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS IAM policies",
                    "Physical security",
                    "Amazon S3 bucket policies",
                    "AWS CloudTrail Logs"
                ],
                "answer": "Physical security"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which feature of the AWS Cloud will support an international company's requirement for low latency to all of its customers?",
                "choices": [
                    "Fault tolerance",
                    "Global reach",
                    "Pay-as-you-go pricing",
                    "High availability"
                ],
                "answer": "Global reach"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is the customer's responsibility under the AWS shared responsibility model?",
                "choices": [
                    "Patching underlying infrastructure",
                    "Physical security",
                    "Patching Amazon EC2 instances",
                    "Patching network infrastructure"
                ],
                "answer": "Patching Amazon EC2 instances"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A customer is using multiple AWS accounts with separate billing. How can the customer take advantage of volume discounts with minimal impact to the AWS resources?",
                "choices": [
                    "Create one global AWS acount and move all AWS resources to tha account.",
                    "Sign up for three years of Reserved Instance pricing up front.",
                    "Use the consolidated billing feature from AWS Organizations.",
                    "Sign up for the AWS Enterprise support plan to get volume discounts."
                ],
                "answer": "Use the consolidated billing feature from AWS Organizations."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are features of Amazon CloudWatch Logs?",
                "choices": [
                    "Summaries by Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)",
                    "Free Amazon Elasticsearch Service analytics",
                    "Provided at no charge",
                    "Real-time monitoring"
                ],
                "answer": "Real-time monitoring"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are features of Amazon CloudWatch Logs?",
                "choices": [
                    "Summaries by Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)",
                    "Free Amazon Elasticsearch Service analytics",
                    "Provided at no charge",
                    "Adjustable retention"
                ],
                "answer": "Adjustable retention"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is an AWS managed Domain Name System (DNS) web service?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Route 53",
                    "Amazon Neptune",
                    "Amazon SageMaker",
                    "Amazon Lightsail"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Route 53"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is an AWS managed Domain Name System (DNS) web service?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Route 53",
                    "Amazon Neptune",
                    "Amazon SageMaker",
                    "Amazon Lightsail"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Route 53"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A customer is deploying a new application and needs to choose an AWS Region. Which of the following factors could influence the customer's decision?",
                "choices": [
                    "Reduced latency to users",
                    "The application's presentation in the local language",
                    "Cooling costs in hotter climates",
                    "Proximity to the customer's office for on-site visits"
                ],
                "answer": "Reduced latency to users"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A customer is deploying a new application and needs to choose an AWS Region. Which of the following factors could influence the customer's decision?",
                "choices": [
                    "Data sovereignty compliance",
                    "The application's presentation in the local language",
                    "Cooling costs in hotter climates",
                    "Proximity to the customer's office for on-site visits"
                ],
                "answer": "Data sovereignty compliance"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which storage service can be used as a low-cost option for hosting static websites?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Glacier",
                    "Amazon DynamoDB",
                    "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)",
                    "Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3)"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3)"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which Amazon EC2 instance pricing model can provide discounts of up to 90%?",
                "choices": [
                    "Reserved Instances",
                    "On-Demand",
                    "Dedicated Hosts",
                    "Spot Instances"
                ],
                "answer": "Spot Instances"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following AWS Cloud services can be used to run a customer-managed relational database?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon EC2",
                    "Amazon Route 53",
                    "Amazon ElastiCache",
                    "Amazon DynamoDB"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon EC2"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A company is looking for a scalable data warehouse solution. Which of the following AWS solutions would meet the company's needs?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3)",
                    "Amazon DynamoDB",
                    "Amazon Kinesis",
                    "Amazon Redshift"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Redshift"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which statement best describes Elastic Load Balancing?",
                "choices": [
                    "It translates a domain name into an IP address using DNS.",
                    "It distributes incoming application traffic across one or more Amazon EC2 instances.",
                    "It collects metrics on connected Amazon EC2 instances.",
                    "It automatically adjusts the number of Amazon EC2 instances to support incoming traffic."
                ],
                "answer": "It distributes incoming application traffic across one or more Amazon EC2 instances."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are valid ways for a customer to interact with AWS services?",
                "choices": [
                    "Command line interface",
                    "On-premises",
                    "Software-as-a-service",
                    "Hybrid"
                ],
                "answer": "Command line interface"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are valid ways for a customer to interact with AWS services?",
                "choices": [
                    "Software Development Kits",
                    "On-premises",
                    "Software-as-a-service",
                    "Hybrid"
                ],
                "answer": "Software Development Kits"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "The AWS Cloud's multiple Regions are an example of:",
                "choices": [
                    "agility.",
                    "global infrastructure.",
                    "elasticity.",
                    "pay-as-you-go pricing."
                ],
                "answer": "global infrastructure."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following AWS services can be used to serve large amounts of online video content with the lowest possible latency?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Storage Gateway",
                    "Amazon S3",
                    "Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)",
                    "Amazon Glacier"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon S3"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following AWS services can be used to serve large amounts of online video content with the lowest possible latency?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Storage Gateway",
                    "Amazom CloudFront",
                    "Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)",
                    "Amazon Glacier"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazom CloudFront"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Web servers running on Amazon EC2 access a legacy application running in a corporate data center. What term would describe this model?",
                "choices": [
                    "Cloud-native",
                    "Partner network",
                    "Hybrid architecture",
                    "Infrastructure as a service"
                ],
                "answer": "Hybrid architecture"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What is the benefit of using AWS managed services, such as Amazon ElastiCache and Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)?",
                "choices": [
                    "They require the customer to monitor and replace failing instances.",
                    "They have better performance than customer-managed services.",
                    "They simplify patching and updating underlying OSs.",
                    "They do not require the customer to optimize instance type or size selections."
                ],
                "answer": "They simplify patching and updating underlying OSs."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which service provides a virtually unlimited amount of online highly durable object storage?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Redshift",
                    "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)",
                    "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)",
                    "Amazon S3"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon S3"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following Identity and Access Management (IAM) entities is associated with an access key ID and secret access key when using AWS Command Line Interface (AWS CLI)?",
                "choices": [
                    "IAM group",
                    "IAM user",
                    "IAM role",
                    "IAM policy"
                ],
                "answer": "IAM user"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following security-related services does AWS offer?",
                "choices": [
                    "Multi-factor authentication physical tokens",
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor security checks",
                    "Automated penetration testing",
                    "Amazon S3 copyrighted content detection"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Trusted Advisor security checks"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following security-related services does AWS offer?",
                "choices": [
                    "Multi-factor authentication physical tokens",
                    "Data encryption",
                    "Automated penetration testing",
                    "Amazon S3 copyrighted content detection"
                ],
                "answer": "Data encryption"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS managed service is used to host databases?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Batch",
                    "AWS Artifact",
                    "AWS Data Pipeline",
                    "Amazon RDS"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon RDS"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service provides a simple and scalable shared file storage solution for use with Linux-based AWS and on-premises servers?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon S3",
                    "Amazon Glacier",
                    "Amazon EBS",
                    "Amazon EFS"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon EFS"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "When architecting cloud applications, which of the following are a key design principle?",
                "choices": [
                    "Use the largest instance possible",
                    "Provision capacity for peak load",
                    "Use the Scrum development process",
                    "Implement elasticity"
                ],
                "answer": "Implement elasticity"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service should be used for long-term, low-cost storage of data backups?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon RDS",
                    "Amazon Glacier",
                    "AWS Snowball",
                    "AWS EBS"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Glacier"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Under the shared responsibility model, which of the following is a shared control between a customer and AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "Physical controls",
                    "Patch management",
                    "Zone security",
                    "Data center auditing"
                ],
                "answer": "Patch management"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service allows companies to connect an Amazon VPC to an on-premises data center?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS VPN",
                    "Amazon Redshift",
                    "API Gateway",
                    "Amazon Direct Connect"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Direct Connect"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A company wants to reduce the physical compute footprint that developers use to run code. Which service would meet that need by enabling serverless architectures?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2)",
                    "AWS Lambda",
                    "Amazon DynamoDB",
                    "AWS CodeCommit"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Lambda"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service provides alerts when an AWS event may impact a company's AWS resources?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Personal Health Dashboard",
                    "AWS Service Health Dashboard",
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor",
                    "AWS Infrastructure Event Management"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Personal Health Dashboard"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are categories of AWS Trusted Advisor?",
                "choices": [
                    "Fault Tolerance",
                    "Instance Usage",
                    "Infrastructure",
                    "Storage Capacity"
                ],
                "answer": "Fault Tolerance"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are categories of AWS Trusted Advisor?",
                "choices": [
                    "Performance",
                    "Instance Usage",
                    "Infrastructure",
                    "Storage Capacity"
                ],
                "answer": "Performance"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are categories of AWS Trusted Advisor?",
                "choices": [
                    "Performance",
                    "Instance Usage",
                    "Infrastructure",
                    "Storage Capacity"
                ],
                "answer": "Performance"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which task is AWS responsible for in the shared responsibility model for security and compliance?",
                "choices": [
                    "Granting access to individuals and services",
                    "Encrypting data in transit",
                    "Updating Amazon EC2 host firmware",
                    "Updating operating systems"
                ],
                "answer": "Updating Amazon EC2 host firmware"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Where should a company go to search software listings from independent software vendors to find, test, buy and deploy software that runs on AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Marketplace",
                    "Amazon Lumberyard",
                    "AWS Artifact",
                    "Amazon CloudSearch"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Marketplace"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is a benefit of using the AWS Cloud?",
                "choices": [
                    "Permissive security removes the administrative burden.",
                    "Ability to focus on revenue-generating activities.",
                    "Control over cloud network hardware.",
                    "Choice of specific cloud hardware vendors."
                ],
                "answer": "Ability to focus on revenue-generating activities."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "When performing a cost analysis that supports physical isolation of a customer workload, which compute hosting model should be accounted for in the Total Cost of Ownership (TCO)?",
                "choices": [
                    "Dedicated Hosts",
                    "Reserved Instances",
                    "On-Demand Instances",
                    "No Upfront Reserved Instances"
                ],
                "answer": "Dedicated Hosts"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service provides the ability to manage infrastructure as code?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS CodePipeline",
                    "AWS CodeDeploy",
                    "AWS Direct Connect",
                    "AWS CloudFormation"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS CloudFormation"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "If a customer needs to audit the change management of AWS resources, which of the following AWS services should the customer use?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Config",
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor",
                    "Amazon CloudWatch",
                    "Amazon Inspector"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Config"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What is Amazon CloudWatch?",
                "choices": [
                    "A code repository with customizable build and team commit features.",
                    "A metrics repository with customizable notification thresholds and channels.",
                    "A security configuration repository with threat analytics.",
                    "A rule repository of a web application firewall with automated vulnerability prevention features."
                ],
                "answer": "A metrics repository with customizable notification thresholds and channels."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which service allows a company with multiple AWS accounts to combine its usage to obtain volume discounts?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Server Migration Service",
                    "AWS Organizations",
                    "AWS Budgets",
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Organizations"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following services could be used to deploy an application to servers running on-premises?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
                    "AWS OpsWorks",
                    "AWS Batch",
                    "AWS X-Ray"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS OpsWorks"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following services could be used to deploy an application to servers running on-premises?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
                    "AWS CodeDeploy",
                    "AWS Batch",
                    "AWS X-Ray"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS CodeDeploy"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which Amazon EC2 pricing model adjusts based on supply and demand of EC2 instances?",
                "choices": [
                    "On-Demand Instances",
                    "Reserved Instances",
                    "Spot Instances",
                    "Convertible Reserved Instances"
                ],
                "answer": "Spot Instances"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which design principles for cloud architecture are recommended when re-architecting a large monolithic application?",
                "choices": [
                    "Use manual monitoring.",
                    "Use fixed servers.",
                    "Design for scalability.",
                    "Rely on individual components."
                ],
                "answer": "Rely on individual components."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which design principles for cloud architecture are recommended when re-architecting a large monolithic application?",
                "choices": [
                    "Use manual monitoring.",
                    "Use fixed servers.",
                    "Implement loose coupling.",
                    " Design for scalability."
                ],
                "answer": "Implement loose coupling."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which is the MINIMUM AWS Support plan that allows for one-hour target response time for support cases?",
                "choices": [
                    "Enterprise",
                    "Business",
                    "Developer",
                    "Basic"
                ],
                "answer": "Business"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Where can AWS compliance and certification reports be downloaded?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Artifact",
                    "AWS Concierge",
                    "AWS Certificate Manager",
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Artifact"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service provides a customized view of the health of specific AWS services that power a customer's workloads running on AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Service Health Dashboard",
                    "AWS X-Ray",
                    "AWS Personal Health Dashboard",
                    "Amazon CloudWatch"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Personal Health Dashboard"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of consolidated billing on AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "Volume pricing qualification",
                    "Shared access permissions",
                    "Multiple bills per account",
                    "Eliminates the need for tagging"
                ],
                "answer": "Volume pricing qualification"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following steps should be taken by a customer when conducting penetration testing on AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "Conduct penetration testing using Amazon Inspector, and then notify AWS support.",
                    "Request and wait for approval from the customer's internal security team, and then conduct testing.",
                    "Notify AWS support, and then conduct testing immediately.",
                    "Request and wait for approval from AWS support, and then conduct testing."
                ],
                "answer": "Request and wait for approval from the customer's internal security team, and then conduct testing."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following AWS features enables a user to launch a pre-configured Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instance?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)",
                    "Amazon Machine Image",
                    "Amazon EC2 Systems Manager",
                    "Amazon AppStream 2.0"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Machine Image"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "How would an AWS customer easily apply common access controls to a large set of users?",
                "choices": [
                    "Apply an IAM policy to an IAM group.",
                    "Apply an IAM policy to an IAM role.",
                    "Apply the same IAM policy to all IAM users with access to the same workload.",
                    "Apply an IAM policy to an Amazon Cognito user pool."
                ],
                "answer": "Apply an IAM policy to an IAM group."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What technology enables compute capacity to adjust as loads change?",
                "choices": [
                    "Load balancing",
                    "Automatic failover",
                    "Round robin",
                    "Auto Scaling"
                ],
                "answer": "Auto Scaling"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services are defined as global instead of regional?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Route 53",
                    "Amazon EC2",
                    "Amazon S3",
                    "Amazon DynamoDB"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Route 53"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services are defined as global instead of regional?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon CloudFront",
                    "Amazon EC2",
                    "Amazon S3",
                    "Amazon DynamoDB"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon CloudFront"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service would you use to obtain compliance reports and certificates?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Artifact",
                    "AWS Lambda",
                    "Amazon Inspector",
                    "AWS Certificate Manager"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Artifact"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Under the shared responsibility model, which of the following tasks are the responsibility of the AWS customer?",
                "choices": [
                    "Ensuring that application data is encrypted at rest",
                    "Ensuring that AWS NTP servers are set to the correct time",
                    "Ensuring that access to data centers is restricted",
                    "Ensuring that hardware is disposed of properly"
                ],
                "answer": "Ensuring that application data is encrypted at rest"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Under the shared responsibility model, which of the following tasks are the responsibility of the AWS customer?",
                "choices": [
                    "Ensuring that users have received security training in the use of AWS services",
                    "Ensuring that AWS NTP servers are set to the correct time",
                    "Ensuring that access to data centers is restricted",
                    "Ensuring that hardware is disposed of properly"
                ],
                "answer": "Ensuring that users have received security training in the use of AWS services"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service can be used to manually launch instances based on resource requirements?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon EBS",
                    "Amazon S3",
                    "Amazon EC2",
                    "Amazon ECS"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon EC2"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A company is migrating an application that is running non-interruptible workloads for a three-year time frame. Which pricing construct would provide the MOST cost-effective solution?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon EC2 Spot Instances",
                    "Amazon EC2 Dedicated Instances",
                    "Amazon EC2 On-Demand Instances",
                    "Amazon EC2 Reserved Instances"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon EC2 Reserved Instances"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "The financial benefits of using AWS are: ",
                "choices": [
                    "reduced Total Cost of Ownership (TCO).",
                    "increased capital expenditure (capex).",
                    "deferred payment plans for startups.",
                    "business credit lines for stratups."
                ],
                "answer": "reduced Total Cost of Ownership (TCO)."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "The financial benefits of using AWS are: ",
                "choices": [
                    "reduced operational expenditure (opex).",
                    "increased capital expenditure (capex).",
                    "deferred payment plans for startups.",
                    "business credit lines for stratups."
                ],
                "answer": "reduced operational expenditure (opex)."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS Cost Management tool allows you to view the most granular data about your AWS bill?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Cost Explorer",
                    "AWS Budgets",
                    "AWS Cost and Usage report",
                    "AWS Billing dashboard"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Cost and Usage report"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following can an AWS customer use to launch a new Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) cluster?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Concierge",
                    "AWS CloudFormation",
                    "Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3)",
                    "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS CloudFormation"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following can an AWS customer use to launch a new Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) cluster?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Concierge",
                    "AWS Management Console",
                    "Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3)",
                    "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Management Console"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is an AWS Cloud architecture design principle?",
                "choices": [
                    "Implement single points of failure.",
                    "Implement loose coupling.",
                    "Implement monolithic design.",
                    "Implement vertical scaling."
                ],
                "answer": "Implement loose coupling."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following security measures protect access to an AWS account?",
                "choices": [
                    "Enable AWS CloudTrail.",
                    "Grant least privilege access to IAM users.",
                    "Create one IAM user and share with many developers and users.",
                    "Enable Amazon CloudFront."
                ],
                "answer": "Grant least privilege access to IAM users."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following security measures protect access to an AWS account?",
                "choices": [
                    "Enable AWS CloudTrail.",
                    "Activate multi-factor authentication (MFA) for privileged users.",
                    "Create one IAM user and share with many developers and users.",
                    "Enable Amazon CloudFront."
                ],
                "answer": "Grant least privilege access to IAM users."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which service provides a hybrid storage service that enables on-premises applications to seamlessly use cloud storage?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Glacier",
                    "AWS Snowball",
                    "AWS Storage Gateway",
                    "Amazon Elastic Block Storage (Amazon EBS)"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Storage Gateway"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following services falls under the responsibility of the customer to maintain operating system configuration, security patching, and networking?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon RDS",
                    "Amazon EC2",
                    "Amazon ElastiCache",
                    "AWS Fargate"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon EC2"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is an important architectural design principle when designing cloud applications?",
                "choices": [
                    "Use multiple Availability Zones.",
                    "Use tightly coupled components.",
                    "Use open source software.",
                    "Provision extra capacity."
                ],
                "answer": "Use multiple Availability Zones."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS support plan includes a dedicated Technical Account Manager?",
                "choices": [
                    "Developer",
                    "Enterprise",
                    "Business",
                    "Basic"
                ],
                "answer": "Enterprise"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) offers which of the following benefits over traditional database management?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS manages the data stored in Amazon RDS tables.",
                    "AWS manages the maintenance of the operating system.",
                    "AWS automatically scales up instance types on demand.",
                    "AWS manages the database type."
                ],
                "answer": "AWS manages the maintenance of the operating system."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which service is best for storing common database query results, which helps to alleviate database access load?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Machine Learning",
                    "Amazon SQS",
                    "Amazon ElastiCache",
                    "Amazon EC2 Instance Store"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon ElastiCache"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is a component of the shared responsibility model managed entirely by AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "Patching operating system software",
                    "Encrypting data",
                    "Enforcing multi-factor authentication",
                    "Auditing physical data center assets"
                ],
                "answer": "Auditing physical data center assets"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which options does AWS make available for customers who want to learn about security in the cloud in an instructor-led setting?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor",
                    "AWS Online Tech Talks",
                    "AWS Blog",
                    "AWS Forums"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Online Tech Talks"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which options does AWS make available for customers who want to learn about security in the cloud in an instructor-led setting?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor",
                    "AWS Classroom Training",
                    "AWS Blog",
                    "AWS Forums"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Classroom Training"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following features can be configured through the Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) Dashboard?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon CloudFront distributions",
                    "Amazon Route 53",
                    "Security Groups",
                    "Elastic Load Balancing"
                ],
                "answer": "Security Groups"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following features can be configured through the Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) Dashboard?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon CloudFront distributions",
                    "Amazon Route 53",
                    "Subnets",
                    "Elastic Load Balancing"
                ],
                "answer": "Subnets"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "If each department within a company has its own AWS account, what is one way to enable consolidated billing?",
                "choices": [
                    "Use AWS Budgets on each account to pay only to budget.",
                    "Contact AWS Support for a monthly bill.",
                    "Create an AWS Organization from the payer account and invite the other accounts to join.",
                    "Put all invoices into one Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) bucket, load data into Amazon Redshift, and then run a billing report."
                ],
                "answer": "Create an AWS Organization from the payer account and invite the other accounts to join."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "How do customers benefit from Amazon's massive economies of scale?",
                "choices": [
                    "Periodic price reductions as the result of Amazon's operational efficiencies",
                    "New Amazon EC2 instance types providing the latest hardware",
                    "The ability to scale up and down when needed",
                    "Increased reliability in the underlying hardware of Amazon EC2 instances"
                ],
                "answer": "Periodic price reductions as the result of Amazon's operational efficiencies"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services can be used to gather information about AWS account activity?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon CloudFront",
                    "AWS Cloud9",
                    "AWS CloudTrail",
                    "AWS CloudHSM"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS CloudTrail"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services can be used to gather information about AWS account activity?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon CloudFront",
                    "AWS Cloud9",
                    "Amazon CloudWatch",
                    "AWS CloudHSM"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon CloudWatch"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following common IT tasks can AWS cover to free up company IT resources?",
                "choices": [
                    "Patching databases software",
                    "Testing application releases",
                    "Backing up databases",
                    "Creating database schema"
                ],
                "answer": "Patching databases software"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following common IT tasks can AWS cover to free up company IT resources?",
                "choices": [
                    "Backing up databases",
                    "Testing application releases",
                    "Running penetration tests",
                    "Creating database schema"
                ],
                "answer": "Backing up databases"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "In which scenario should Amazon EC2 Spot Instances be used?",
                "choices": [
                    "A company wants to move its main website to AWS from an on-premises web server.",
                    "A company has a number of application services whose Service Level Agreement (SLA) requires 99.999% uptime.",
                    "A company's heavily used legacy database is currently running on-premises.",
                    "A company has a number of infrequent, interruptible jobs that are currently using On-Demand Instances."
                ],
                "answer": "A company has a number of infrequent, interruptible jobs that are currently using On-Demand Instances."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS feature should a customer leverage to achieve high availability of an application?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Direct Connect",
                    "Availability Zones",
                    "Data centers",
                    "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC)"
                ],
                "answer": "Availability Zones"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service can serve a static website?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon S3",
                    "Amazon Route 53",
                    "Amazon QuickSight",
                    "AWS X-Ray"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon S3"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "How does AWS shorten the time to provision IT resources?",
                "choices": [
                    "It supplies an online IT ticketing platform for resource requests.",
                    "It supports automatic code validation services.",
                    "It provides the ability to programmatically provision existing resources.",
                    "It automates the resource request process from a company's IT vendor list."
                ],
                "answer": "It provides the ability to programmatically provision existing resources."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What can AWS edge locations be used for?",
                "choices": [
                    "Hosting applications",
                    "Delivering content closer to users",
                    "Running NoSQL database caching services",
                    "Sending notification messages to end users"
                ],
                "answer": "Delivering content closer to users"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What can AWS edge locations be used for?",
                "choices": [
                    "Hosting applications",
                    "Reducing traffic on the server by caching responses",
                    "Running NoSQL database caching services",
                    "Sending notification messages to end users"
                ],
                "answer": "Reducing traffic on the server by caching responses"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following can limit Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) bucket access to specific users?",
                "choices": [
                    "A public and private key-pair",
                    "Amazon Inspector",
                    "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) policies",
                    "Security Groups"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) policies"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A solution that is able to support growth in users, traffic, or data size with no drop in performance aligns with which cloud architecture principle?",
                "choices": [
                    "Think parallel",
                    "Implement elasticity",
                    "Decouple your components",
                    "Design for failure"
                ],
                "answer": "Implement elasticity"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A company will be moving from an on-premises data center to the AWS Cloud. What would be one financial difference after the move?",
                "choices": [
                    "Moving from variable operational expense (opex) to upfront capital expense (capex).",
                    "Moving from upfront capital expense (capex) to variable capital expense (capex).",
                    "Moving from upfront capital expense (capex) to variable operational expense (opex).",
                    "Elimination of upfront capital expense (capex) and elimination of variable operational expense (opex)"
                ],
                "answer": "Moving from upfront capital expense (capex) to variable operational expense (opex)."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "How should a customer forecast the future costs for running a new web application?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Aurora Backtrack",
                    "Amazon CloudWatch Billing Alarms",
                    "AWS Simple Monthly Calculator",
                    "AWS Cost and Usage report"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Simple Monthly Calculator"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which is the MINIMUM AWS Support plan that provides technical support through phone calls?",
                "choices": [
                    "Enterprise",
                    "Business",
                    "Developer",
                    "Basic"
                ],
                "answer": "Business"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following tasks is the responsibility of AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "Encrypting client-side data",
                    "Configuring AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) roles",
                    "Securing the Amazon EC2 hypervisor",
                    "Setting user password policies"
                ],
                "answer": "Securing the Amazon EC2 hypervisor"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "One benefit of On-Demand Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) pricing is:",
                "choices": [
                    "the ability to bid for a lower hourly cost.",
                    "paying a daily rate regardless of time used.",
                    "paying only for time used.",
                    "pre-paying for instances and paying a lower hourly rate."
                ],
                "answer": "paying only for time used."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "An administrator needs to rapidly deploy a popular IT solution and start using it immediately. Where can the administrator find assistance?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Well-Architected Framework documentation",
                    "Amazon CloudFront",
                    "AWS CodeCommit",
                    "AWS Quick Start reference deployments"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Quick Start reference deployments"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following services is in the category of AWS serverless platform?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon EMR",
                    "Elastic Load Balancing",
                    "AWS Lambda",
                    "AWS Mobile Hub"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Lambda"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following services is in the category of AWS serverless platform?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon EMR",
                    "Elastic Load Balancing",
                    "AWS Lambda",
                    "AWS Mobile Hub"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Lambda"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which services are parts of the AWS serverless platform?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon EC2, Amazon S3, Amazon Athena",
                    "Amazon Kinesis, Amazon SQS, Amazon EMR",
                    "AWS Step Functions, Amazon DynamoDB, Amazon SNS",
                    "Amazon Athena, Amazon Cognito, Amazon EC2"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Step Functions, Amazon DynamoDB, Amazon SNS"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "According to the AWS shared responsibility model, what is the sole responsibility of AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "Application security",
                    "Edge location management",
                    "Patch management",
                    "Client-side data"
                ],
                "answer": "Edge location management"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS IAM feature is used to associate a set of permissions with multiple users?",
                "choices": [
                    "Multi-factor authentication",
                    "Groups",
                    "Password policies",
                    "Access keys"
                ],
                "answer": "Groups"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are benefits of the AWS Cloud?",
                "choices": [
                    "Unlimited uptime",
                    "Elasticity",
                    "Colocation",
                    "Capital expenses"
                ],
                "answer": "Elasticity"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are benefits of the AWS Cloud?",
                "choices": [
                    "Unlimited uptime",
                    "Agility",
                    "Colocation",
                    "Capital expenses"
                ],
                "answer": "Agility"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following can a customer use to enable single sign-on (SSO) to the AWS Console?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Connect",
                    "AWS Directory Service",
                    "Amazon Pinpoint",
                    "Amazon Recognition"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Directory Service"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What are the multiple, isolated locations within an AWS Region that are connected by low-latency networks called?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Direct Connects",
                    "Amazon VPCs",
                    "Edge locations",
                    "Availability Zones"
                ],
                "answer": "Availability Zones"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following benefits does the AWS Compliance program provide to AWS customers?",
                "choices": [
                    "It verifies that hosted workloads are automatically compliant with the controls of supported compliance frameworks.",
                    "AWS is responsible for the maintenance of common compliance framework documentation.",
                    "It ensures the use of compliance frameworks that are being used by other cloud providers.",
                    "It will adopt new compliance frameworks as they become relevant to customer workloads."
                ],
                "answer": "AWS is responsible for the maintenance of common compliance framework documentation."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following benefits does the AWS Compliance program provide to AWS customers?",
                "choices": [
                    "It verifies that hosted workloads are automatically compliant with the controls of supported compliance frameworks.",
                    "It assures customers that AWS is maintaining physical security and data protection.",
                    "It ensures the use of compliance frameworks that are being used by other cloud providers.",
                    "It will adopt new compliance frameworks as they become relevant to customer workloads."
                ],
                "answer": "It assures customers that AWS is maintaining physical security and data protection."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following services provides on-demand access to AWS compliance reports?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS IAM",
                    "AWS Artifact",
                    "Amazon GuardDuty",
                    "AWS KMS"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Artifact"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "As part of the AWS shared responsibility model, which of the following operational controls do users fully inherit from AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "Security management of data center",
                    "Patch management",
                    "Configuration management",
                    "User and access management"
                ],
                "answer": "User and access management"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "When comparing AWS Cloud with on-premises Total Cost of Ownership, which expenses must be considered?",
                "choices": [
                    "Software development",
                    "Project management",
                    "Storage hardware",
                    "Antivirus software license"
                ],
                "answer": "Storage hardware"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "When comparing AWS Cloud with on-premises Total Cost of Ownership, which expenses must be considered?",
                "choices": [
                    "Software development",
                    "Project management",
                    "Physical servers",
                    "Antivirus software license"
                ],
                "answer": "Physical servers"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Under the shared responsibility model, which of the following tasks are the responsibility of the customer?",
                "choices": [
                    "Maintaining the underlying Amazon EC2 hardware.",
                    "Managing the VPC network access control lists.",
                    "Replacing failed hard disk drives.",
                    "Deploying hardware in different Availability Zones."
                ],
                "answer": "Managing the VPC network access control lists."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Under the shared responsibility model, which of the following tasks are the responsibility of the customer?",
                "choices": [
                    "Maintaining the underlying Amazon EC2 hardware.",
                    "Encrypting data in transit and at rest.",
                    "Replacing failed hard disk drives.",
                    "Deploying hardware in different Availability Zones."
                ],
                "answer": "Encrypting data in transit and at rest."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which scenarios represent the concept of elasticity on AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "Scaling the number of Amazon EC2 instances based on traffic.",
                    "Resizing Amazon RDS instances as business needs change.",
                    "Using AWS compliance documents to accelerate the compliance process.",
                    "Having the ability to create and govern environments using code."
                ],
                "answer": "Scaling the number of Amazon EC2 instances based on traffic."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which scenarios represent the concept of elasticity on AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "Automatically directing traffic to less-utilized Amazon EC2 instances.",
                    "Resizing Amazon RDS instances as business needs change.",
                    "Using AWS compliance documents to accelerate the compliance process.",
                    "Having the ability to create and govern environments using code."
                ],
                "answer": "Automatically directing traffic to less-utilized Amazon EC2 instances."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "When is it beneficial for a company to use a Spot Instance?",
                "choices": [
                    "When there is flexibility in when an application needs to run.",
                    "When there are mission-critical workloads.",
                    "When dedicated capacity is needed.",
                    "When an instance should not be stopped."
                ],
                "answer": "When there is flexibility in when an application needs to run."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A company is considering moving its on-premises data center to AWS. What factors should be included in doing a Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) analysis?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon EC2 instance availability",
                    "Power consumption of the data center",
                    "Application developer time",
                    "Database engine capacity"
                ],
                "answer": "Power consumption of the data center"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "When is it beneficial for a company to use a Spot Instance?",
                "choices": [
                    "When there is flexibility in when an application needs to run.",
                    "Labor costs to replace old servers",
                    "Application developer time",
                    "Database engine capacity"
                ],
                "answer": "Labor costs to replace old servers"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "How does AWS charge for AWS Lambda?",
                "choices": [
                    "Users bid on the maximum price they are willing to pay per hour.",
                    "Users choose a 1-, 3- or 5-year upfront payment term.",
                    "Users pay for the required permanent storage on a file system or in a database.",
                    "Users pay based on the number of requests and consumed compute resources."
                ],
                "answer": "Users pay based on the number of requests and consumed compute resources."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What function do security groups serve related Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instance security?",
                "choices": [
                    "Act as a virtual firewall for the Amazon EC2 instance.",
                    "Secure AWS user accounts with AWS identity and Access Management (IAM) policies.",
                    "Provide DDoS protection with AWS Shield.",
                    "Use Amazon CloudFront to protect the Amazon EC2 instance."
                ],
                "answer": "Act as a virtual firewall for the Amazon EC2 instance."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which disaster recovery scenario offers the lowest probability of down time?",
                "choices": [
                    "Backup and restore",
                    "Pilot light",
                    "Warm standby",
                    "Multi-site active-active"
                ],
                "answer": "Multi-site active-active"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What will help a company perform a cost benefit analysis of migrating to the AWS Cloud?",
                "choices": [
                    "Cost Explorer",
                    "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator",
                    "AWS Simple Monthly Calculator",
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following provides the ability to share the cost benefits of Reserved Instances across AWS accounts?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Cost Explorer between AWS accounts",
                    "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator",
                    "AWS Simple Monthly Calculator",
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A company has multiple AWS accounts and wants to simplify and consolidate its billing process. Which AWS service will achieve this?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Cost and Usage Reports",
                    "AWS Organizations",
                    "AWS Cost Explorer",
                    "AWS Budgets"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Organizations"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A company is designing an application hosted in a single AWS Region serving end-users spread across the world. The company wants to provide the end-users low latency access to the application data.Which of the following services will help fulfill this requirement?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon CloudFront",
                    "AWS Direct Connect",
                    "Amazon Route 53 global DNS",
                    "Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) transfer acceleration"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS CloudFront"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following deployment models enables customers to fully trade their capital IT expenses for operational expenses?",
                "choices": [
                    "On-premises",
                    "Hybrid",
                    "Cloud",
                    "Platform as a service"
                ],
                "answer": "Cloud"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "How is asset management on AWS easier than asset management in a physical data center?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS provides a Configuration Management Database that users can maintain.",
                    "AWS performs infrastructure discovery scans on the customer's behalf.",
                    "Amazon EC2 automatically generates an asset report and places it in the customer's specified Amazon S3 bucket.",
                    "Users can gather asset metadata reliably with a few API calls."
                ],
                "answer": "AWS performs infrastructure discovery scans on the customer's behalf."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What feature of Amazon RDS helps to create globally redundant databases?",
                "choices": [
                    "Snapshots",
                    "Automatic patching and updating",
                    "Cross-Region read replicas",
                    "Provisioned IOPS"
                ],
                "answer": "Cross-Region read replicas"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What feature of Amazon RDS helps to create globally redundant databases?",
                "choices": [
                    "Snapshots",
                    "Automatic patching and updating",
                    "Cross-Region read replicas",
                    "Provisioned IOPS"
                ],
                "answer": "Cross-Region read replicas"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Using AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) to grant access only to the resources needed to perform a task is a concept known as:",
                "choices": [
                    "restricted access.",
                    "as-needed access.",
                    "least privilege access.",
                    "token access."
                ],
                "answer": "least privilege access."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which methods can be used to identify AWS costs by departments?",
                "choices": [
                    "Enable multi-factor authentication for the AWS account root user.",
                    "Create separate accounts for each department.",
                    "Use Reserved Instances whenever possible.",
                    "Pay bills using purchase orders."
                ],
                "answer": "Create separate accounts for each department."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which methods can be used to identify AWS costs by departments?",
                "choices": [
                    "Enable multi-factor authentication for the AWS account root user.",
                    "Use tags to associate each instance with a particular department.",
                    "Use Reserved Instances whenever possible.",
                    "Pay bills using purchase orders."
                ],
                "answer": "Use tags to associate each instance with a particular department."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Under the AWS shared responsibility model, customer responsibilities include which one of the following?",
                "choices": [
                    "Securing the hardware, software, facilities, and networks that run all products and services.",
                    "Providing certificates, reports, and other documentation directly to AWS customers under NDA.",
                    "Configuring the operating system, network, and firewall.",
                    "Pay bills using purchase orders."
                ],
                "answer": "Configuring the operating system, network, and firewall."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which managed AWS service provides real-time guidance on AWS security best practices?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS X-Ray",
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor",
                    "Amazon CloudWatch",
                    "AWS Systems Manager"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Trusted Advisor"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which feature adds elasticity to Amazon EC2 instances to handle the changing demand for workloads?",
                "choices": [
                    "Resource groups",
                    "Lifecycle policies",
                    "Application Load Balancer",
                    "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Under the AWS shared responsibility model, customers are responsible for which aspects of security in the cloud?",
                "choices": [
                    "Visualization management",
                    "Hardware management",
                    "Encryption management",
                    "Facilities management"
                ],
                "answer": "Encryption management"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Under the AWS shared responsibility model, customers are responsible for which aspects of security in the cloud?",
                "choices": [
                    "Visualization management",
                    "Hardware management",
                    "Firewall management",
                    "Facilities management"
                ],
                "answer": "Firewall management"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS hybrid storage service enables on-premises applications to seamlessly use AWS Cloud storage through standard file-storage protocols?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Direct Connect",
                    "AWS Snowball",
                    "AWS Storage Gateway",
                    "AWS Snowball Edge"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Storage Gateway"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What is a responsibility of AWS in the shared responsibility model?",
                "choices": [
                    "Updating the network ACLs to block traffic to vulnerable ports.",
                    "Patching operating systems running on Amazon EC2 instances.",
                    "Updating the firmware on the underlying EC2 hosts.",
                    "Updating the security group rules to block traffic to the vulnerable ports."
                ],
                "answer": "Updating the firmware on the underlying EC2 hosts."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which architectural principle is used when deploying an Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) instance in Multiple Availability Zone mode?",
                "choices": [
                    "Implement loose coupling.",
                    "Design for failure.",
                    "Automate everything that can be automated.",
                    "Use services, not servers."
                ],
                "answer": "Design for failure."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What does it mean to grant least privilege to AWS IAM users?",
                "choices": [
                    "It is granting permissions to a single user only.",
                    "It is granting permissions using AWS IAM policies only.",
                    "It is granting AdministratorAccess policy permissions to trustworthy users.",
                    "It is granting only the permissions required to perform a given task."
                ],
                "answer": "It is granting only the permissions required to perform a given task."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What is a benefit of loose coupling as a principle of cloud architecture design?",
                "choices": [
                    "It facilitates low-latency request handling.",
                    "It allows applications to have dependent workflows.",
                    "It prevents cascading failures between different components.",
                    "It allows companies to focus on their physical data center operations."
                ],
                "answer": "It prevents cascading failures between different components."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A director has been tasked with investigating hybrid cloud architecture. The company currently accesses AWS over the public internet. Which service will facilitate private hybrid connectivity? Applying which AWS Cloud design principle will address the current design issue?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) NAT Gateway",
                    "AWS Direct Connect",
                    "Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) Transfer Acceleration",
                    "AWS Web Application Firewall (AWS WAF)"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Direct Connect"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A company's web application currently has tight dependencies on underlying components, so when one component fails the entire web application fails.",
                "choices": [
                    "Implementing elasticity, enabling the application to scale up or scale down as demand changes.",
                    "Enabling several EC2 instances to run in parallel to achieve better performance.",
                    "Focusing on decoupling components by isolating them and ensuring individual components can function when other components fail.",
                    "Doubling EC2 computing resources to increase system fault tolerance."
                ],
                "answer": "Focusing on decoupling components by isolating them and ensuring individual components can function when other components fail."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "How can a customer increase security to AWS account logons?",
                "choices": [
                    "Configure AWS Certificate Manager",
                    "Enable Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)",
                    "Use Amazon Cognito to manage access",
                    "Enable AWS Organizations"
                ],
                "answer": "Enable Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "How can a customer increase security to AWS account logons?",
                "choices": [
                    "Configure AWS Certificate Manager",
                    "Use Amazon Cognito to manage access",
                    "Use Amazon Cognito to manage access",
                    "Enable AWS Organizations"
                ],
                "answer": "Use Amazon Cognito to manage access"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What AWS service would be used to centrally manage AWS access across multiple accounts?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Service Catalog",
                    "AWS Config",
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor",
                    "AWS Organizations"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Organizations"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service can a customer use to set up an alert notification when the account is approaching a particular dollar amount?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Cost and Usage reports",
                    "AWS Budgets",
                    "AWS Cost Explorer",
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Budgets"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What can users access from AWS Artifact?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS security and compliance documents",
                    "A download of configuration management details for all AWS resources",
                    "Training materials for AWS services",
                    "A security assessment of the applications deployed in the AWS Cloud"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS security and compliance documents"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What can users access from AWS Artifact?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS security and compliance documents",
                    "A download of configuration management details for all AWS resources",
                    "Training materials for AWS services",
                    "A security assessment of the applications deployed in the AWS Cloud"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS security and compliance documents"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which is the MINIMUM AWS Support plan that provides designated Technical Account Managers?",
                "choices": [
                    "Enterprise",
                    "Business",
                    "Developer",
                    "Basic"
                ],
                "answer": "Enterprise"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is an AWS Well-Architected Framework design principle related to reliability?",
                "choices": [
                    "Deployment to a single Availability Zone",
                    "Ability to recover from failure",
                    "Design for cost optimization",
                    "Perform operations as code"
                ],
                "answer": "Ability to recover from failure"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which type of AWS storage is ephemeral and is deleted when an instance is stopped or terminated?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon EBS",
                    "Amazon EC2 instance store",
                    "Amazon EFS",
                    "Amazon S3"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon EC2 instance store"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What is an advantage of using the AWS Cloud over a traditional on-premises solution?",
                "choices": [
                    "Users do not have to guess about future capacity needs.",
                    "Users can utilize existing hardware contracts for purchases.",
                    "Users can fix costs no matter what their traffic is.",
                    "Users can avoid audits by using reports from AWS."
                ],
                "answer": "Users do not have to guess about future capacity needs."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is an AWS-managed compute service?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon SWF",
                    "Amazon EC2",
                    "AWS Glacier",
                    "Amazon Aurora"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon EC2"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is an AWS-managed compute service?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon SWF",
                    "AWS Glacier",
                    "AWS Lambda",
                    "Amazon Aurora"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Lambda"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is an important architectural principle when designing cloud applications?",
                "choices": [
                    "Store data and backups in the same region.",
                    "Design tightly coupled system components.",
                    "Avoid multi-threading.",
                    "Design for failure"
                ],
                "answer": "Design for failure"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which mechanism allows developers to access AWS services from application code?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Software Development Kit",
                    "AWS Management Console",
                    "AWS CodePipeline",
                    "AWS Config"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Software Development Kit"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which Amazon EC2 pricing model is the MOST cost efficient for an uninterruptible workload that runs once a year for 24 hours?",
                "choices": [
                    "On-Demand Instances",
                    "Reserved Instances",
                    "Spot Instances",
                    "Dedicated Instances"
                ],
                "answer": "On-Demand Instances"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following services is a MySQL-compatible database that automatically grows storage as needed?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2)",
                    "Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) for MySQL",
                    "Amazon Lightsail",
                    "Amazon Aurora"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Aurora"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) feature enables users to connect two VPCs together?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon VPC endpoints",
                    "Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) ClassicLink",
                    "Amazon VPC peering",
                    "AWS Direct Connect"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon VPC peering"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which service's PRIMARY purpose is software version control?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon CodeStar",
                    "AWS Command Line Interface (AWS CLI)",
                    "Amazon Cognito",
                    "AWS CodeCommit"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS CodeCommit"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A company is considering migrating its applications to AWS. The company wants to compare the cost of running the workload on-premises to running the equivalent workload on the AWS platform.Which tool can be used to perform this comparison?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Simple Monthly Calculator",
                    "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator",
                    "AWS Billing and Cost Management console",
                    "Cost Explorer"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service provides a secure, fast, and cost-effective way to migrate or transport exabyte-scale datasets into AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Batch",
                    "AWS Snowball",
                    "AWS Migration Hub",
                    "AWS Snowmobile"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Snowmobile"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following BEST describe the AWS pricing model?",
                "choices": [
                    "Fixed-term",
                    "Pay-as-you-go",
                    "Colocation",
                    "Planned"
                ],
                "answer": "Pay-as-you-go"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following BEST describe the AWS pricing model?",
                "choices": [
                    "Fixed-term",
                    "Variable cost",
                    "Colocation",
                    "Planned"
                ],
                "answer": "Variable cost"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which load balancer types are available with Elastic Load Balancing (ELB)?",
                "choices": [
                    "Public load balancers with AWS Application Auto Scaling capabilities",
                    "F5 Big-IP and Citrix NetScaler load balancers",
                    "Classic Load Balancers",
                    "Cross-zone load balancers with public and private IPs"
                ],
                "answer": "Classic Load Balancers"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which load balancer types are available with Elastic Load Balancing (ELB)?",
                "choices": [
                    "Public load balancers with AWS Application Auto Scaling capabilities",
                    "F5 Big-IP and Citrix NetScaler load balancers",
                    "Application Load Balancers",
                    "Cross-zone load balancers with public and private IPs"
                ],
                "answer": "Application Load Balancers"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Why should a company choose AWS instead of a traditional data center?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS provides users with full control over the underlying resources.",
                    "AWS does not require long-term contracts and provides a pay-as-you-go model.",
                    "AWS offers edge locations in every country, supporting global reach.",
                    "AWS has no limits on the number of resources that can be created."
                ],
                "answer": "AWS does not require long-term contracts and provides a pay-as-you-go model."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which solution provides the FASTEST application response times to frequently accessed data to users in multiple AWS Regions?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS CloudTrail across multiple Availability Zones",
                    "Amazon CloudFront to edge locations",
                    "AWS CloudFormation in multiple regions",
                    "A virtual private gateway over AWS Direct Connect"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon CloudFront to edge locations"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service provides a self-service portal for on-demand access to AWS compliance reports?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Config",
                    "AWS Certificate Manager",
                    "Amazon Inspector",
                    "AWS Artifact"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Artifact"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following AWS services can be used to run a self-managed database?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Route 53",
                    "AWS X-Ray",
                    "AWS Snowmobile",
                    "Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2)"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2)"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What exclusive benefit is provided to users with Enterprise Support?",
                "choices": [
                    "Access to a Technical Project Manager",
                    "Access to a Technical Account Manager",
                    "Access to a Cloud Support Engineer",
                    "Access to a Solutions Architect"
                ],
                "answer": "Access to a Technical Account Manager"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "How can a user protect against AWS service disruptions if a natural disaster affects an entire geographic area?",
                "choices": [
                    "Deploy applications across multiple Availability Zones within an AWS Region.",
                    "Use a hybrid cloud computing deployment model within the geographic area.",
                    "Deploy applications across multiple AWS Regions.",
                    "Store application artifacts using AWS Artifact and replicate them across multiple AWS Regions."
                ],
                "answer": "Deploy applications across multiple AWS Regions."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "How does AWS MOST effectively reduce computing costs for a growing start-up company?",
                "choices": [
                    "It provides on-demand resources for peak usage.",
                    "It automates the provisioning of individual developer environments.",
                    "It automates customer relationship management.",
                    "It implements a fixed monthly computing budget."
                ],
                "answer": "It provides on-demand resources for peak usage."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A startup is working on a new application that needs to go to market quickly. The application requirements may need to be adjusted in the near future. Which of the following is a characteristic of the AWS Cloud that would meet this specific need?",
                "choices": [
                    "Elasticity",
                    "Reliability",
                    "Performance",
                    "Agility"
                ],
                "answer": "Agility"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS Support plan provides a full set of AWS Trusted Advisor checks?",
                "choices": [
                    "Business and Developer Support",
                    "Business and Basic Support",
                    "Enterprise and Developer Support",
                    "Enterprise and Business Support"
                ],
                "answer": "Enterprise and Business Support"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following services have Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) mitigation features?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS WAF",
                    "Amazon DynamoDB",
                    "Amazon EC2",
                    "Amazon Inspector"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon EC2"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following services have Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) mitigation features?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS WAF",
                    "Amazon DynamoDB",
                    "Amazon CloudFront",
                    "Amazon Inspector"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon CloudFront"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following services have Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) mitigation features?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS WAF",
                    "Amazon DynamoDB",
                    "Amazon CloudFront",
                    "Amazon Inspector"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon CloudFront"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following services have Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) mitigation features?",
                "choices": [
                    "Compute costs",
                    "Facilities costs",
                    "Data transfer costs",
                    "Hardware lifecycle costs"
                ],
                "answer": "Compute costs"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following services have Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) mitigation features?",
                "choices": [
                    "Storage costs",
                    "Facilities costs",
                    "Data transfer costs",
                    "Hardware lifecycle costs"
                ],
                "answer": "Storage costs"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following services have Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) mitigation features?",
                "choices": [
                    "Data transfer costs",
                    "Facilities costs",
                    "Data transfer costs",
                    "Hardware lifecycle costs"
                ],
                "answer": "Data transfer costs"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What time-savings advantage is offered with the use of Amazon Recognition?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Rekognition provides automatic watermarking of images.",
                    "Amazon Rekognition provides automatic detection of objects appearing in pictures.",
                    "Amazon Rekognition provides the ability to resize millions of images automatically.",
                    "Amazon Rekognition uses Amazon Mechanical Turk to allow humans to bid on object detection jobs."
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Rekognition provides automatic detection of objects appearing in pictures."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "When comparing AWS with on-premises Total Cost of Ownership (TCO), what costs are included?",
                "choices": [
                    "Data center security",
                    "Business analysis",
                    "Project management",
                    "Operating system administration"
                ],
                "answer": "Data center security"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "According to the AWS shared responsibility model, what is AWS responsible for?",
                "choices": [
                    "Configuring Amazon VPC",
                    "Managing application code",
                    "Maintaining application traffic",
                    "Managing the network infrastructure"
                ],
                "answer": "Managing the network infrastructure"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which service should be used to estimate the costs of running a new project on AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS TCO Calculator",
                    "AWS Simple Monthly Calculator",
                    "AWS Simple Monthly Calculator",
                    "AWS Budgets"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Simple Monthly Calculator"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS tool will identify security groups that grant unrestricted Internet access to a limited list of ports?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Organizations",
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor",
                    "AWS Usage Report",
                    "Amazon EC2 dashboard"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon EC2 dashboard"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service can be used to generate alerts based on an estimated monthly bill?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Config",
                    "Amazon CloudWatch",
                    "AWS X-Ray",
                    "AWS CloudTrail"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon CloudWatch"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which Amazon EC2 pricing model offers the MOST significant discount when compared to On-Demand Instances?",
                "choices": [
                    "Partial Upfront Reserved Instances for a 1-year term",
                    "All Upfront Reserved Instances for a 1-year term",
                    "All Upfront Reserved Instances for a 3-year term",
                    "No Upfront Reserved Instances for a 3-year term"
                ],
                "answer": "All Upfront Reserved Instances for a 3-year term"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is the responsibility of AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "Setting up AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) users and groups",
                    "Physically destroying storage media at end of life",
                    "Patching guest operating systems",
                    "Configuring security settings on Amazon EC2 instances"
                ],
                "answer": "Physically destroying storage media at end of life"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of using AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS audits user data.",
                    "Data is automatically secure.",
                    "There is no guessing on capacity needs.",
                    "AWS manages compliance needs."
                ],
                "answer": "There is no guessing on capacity needs."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service would a customer use with a static website to achieve lower latency and high transfer speeds?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Lambda",
                    "Amazon DynamoDB Accelerator",
                    "Amazon Route 53",
                    "Amazon CloudFront"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon CloudFront"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which services manage and automate application deployments on AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
                    "AWS CodeCommit",
                    "AWS Data Pipeline",
                    "AWS Config"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Elastic Beanstalk"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which services manage and automate application deployments on AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS CloudFormation",
                    "AWS CodeCommit",
                    "AWS Data Pipeline",
                    "AWS Config"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS CloudFormation"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A user wants guidance on possible savings when migrating from on-premises to AWS. Which tool is suitable for this scenario?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Budgets",
                    "Cost Explorer",
                    "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator",
                    "AWS Well-Architected Tool"
                ],
                "answer": "Cost Explorer"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which principles are used to architect applications for reliability on the AWS Cloud?",
                "choices": [
                    "Design for automated failure recovery",
                    "Manage changes via documented processes",
                    "Test for moderate demand to ensure reliability",
                    "Backup recovery to an on-premises environment"
                ],
                "answer": "Design for automated failure recovery"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which principles are used to architect applications for reliability on the AWS Cloud?",
                "choices": [
                    "Use multiple Availability Zones",
                    "Manage changes via documented processes",
                    "Test for moderate demand to ensure reliability",
                    "Backup recovery to an on-premises environment"
                ],
                "answer": "Use multiple Availability Zones"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What tasks should a customer perform when that customer suspects an AWS account has been compromised?",
                "choices": [
                    "Rotate passwords and access keys.",
                    "Remove MFA tokens.",
                    "Move resources to a different AWS Region.",
                    "Delete AWS CloudTrail Resources."
                ],
                "answer": "Rotate passwords and access keys."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What tasks should a customer perform when that customer suspects an AWS account has been compromised?",
                "choices": [
                    "Contact AWS Support.",
                    "Remove MFA tokens.",
                    "Move resources to a different AWS Region.",
                    "Delete AWS CloudTrail Resources."
                ],
                "answer": "Contact AWS Support."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What is an example of high availability in the AWS Cloud?",
                "choices": [
                    "Consulting AWS technical support at any time day or night",
                    "Ensuring an application remains accessible, even if a resource fails",
                    "Making any AWS service available for use by paying on demand",
                    "Deploying in any part of the world using AWS Regions"
                ],
                "answer": "Ensuring an application remains accessible, even if a resource fails"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS security service protects applications from distributed denial of service attacks with always-on detection and automatic inline mitigations?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Inspector",
                    "AWS Web Application Firewall (AWS WAF)",
                    "Elastic Load Balancing (ELB)",
                    "AWS Shield"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Shield"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A company wants to monitor the CPU usage of its Amazon EC2 resources. Which AWS service should the company use?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS CloudTrail",
                    "Amazon CloudWatch",
                    "AWS Cost and Usage report",
                    "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon CloudWatch"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What is an AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) role?",
                "choices": [
                    "A user associated with an AWS resource",
                    "A group associated with an AWS resource",
                    "An entity that defines a set of permissions for use with an AWS resource",
                    "An authentication credential associated with a multi-factor authentication (MFA) token"
                ],
                "answer": "An entity that defines a set of permissions for use with an AWS resource"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What are the advantages of Reserved Instances?",
                "choices": [
                    "They provide a discount over on-demand pricing.",
                    "They provide access to additional instance types.",
                    "They provide additional networking capability.",
                    "Customers can upgrade instances as new types become available."
                ],
                "answer": "They provide a discount over on-demand pricing."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What are the advantages of Reserved Instances?",
                "choices": [
                    "Customers can reserve capacity in an Availability Zone.",
                    "They provide access to additional instance types.",
                    "They provide additional networking capability.",
                    "Customers can upgrade instances as new types become available."
                ],
                "answer": "Customers can reserve capacity in an Availability Zone."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "How do Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling groups help achieve high availability for a web application?",
                "choices": [
                    "They automatically add more instances across multiple AWS Regions based on global demand of the application.",
                    "They automatically add or replace instances across multiple Availability Zones when the application needs it.",
                    "They enable the application's static content to reside closer to end users.",
                    "They are able to distribute incoming requests across a tier of web server instances."
                ],
                "answer": "They automatically add or replace instances across multiple Availability Zones when the application needs it."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "How can one AWS account use Reserved Instances from another AWS account?",
                "choices": [
                    "By using Amazon EC2 Dedicated Instances",
                    "By using AWS Organizations consolidated billing",
                    "By using the AWS Cost Explorer tool",
                    "By using AWS Budgets"
                ],
                "answer": "By using AWS Organizations consolidated billing"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following AWS services provide compute resources?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Lambda",
                    "AWS CodeDeploy",
                    "Amazon Glacier",
                    "AWS Organizations"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Lambda"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following AWS services provide compute resources?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)",
                    "AWS CodeDeploy",
                    "Amazon Glacier",
                    "AWS Organizations"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service enables users to deploy infrastructure as code by automating the process of provisioning resources?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon GameLift",
                    "AWS CloudFormation",
                    "AWS Data Pipeline",
                    "AWS Glue"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS CloudFormation"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services provide a way to extend an on-premises architecture to the AWS Cloud?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon EBS",
                    "AWS Direct Connect",
                    "Amazon CloudFront",
                    "Amazon Connect"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Direct Connect"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services provide a way to extend an on-premises architecture to the AWS Cloud?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon EBS",
                    "AWS Storage Gateway",
                    "Amazon CloudFront",
                    "Amazon Connect"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Storage Gateway"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following allows users to provision a dedicated network connection from their internal network to AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS CloudHSM",
                    "AWS Direct Connect",
                    "AWS VPN",
                    "Amazon Connect"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Direct Connect"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which services use AWS edge locations?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon CloudFront",
                    "Amazon EC2",
                    "Amazon RDS",
                    "Amazon ElastiCache"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon CloudFront"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which services use AWS edge locations?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon CloudFront",
                    "AWS Shield",
                    "Amazon RDS",
                    "Amazon ElastiCache"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Shield"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which service would provide network connectivity in a hybrid architecture that includes the AWS Cloud?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon VPC",
                    "AWS Direct Connect",
                    "AWS Directory Service",
                    "Amazon API Gateway"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Direct Connect"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which tool can be used to compare the costs of running a web application in a traditional hosting environment to running it on AWS?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Cost Explorer",
                    "AWS Budgets",
                    "AWS Cost and Usage report",
                    "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What is the value of using third-party software from AWS Marketplace instead of installing third-party software on Amazon EC2?",
                "choices": [
                    "Users pay for software by the hour or month depending on licensing.",
                    "AWS Marketplace data encryption is managed by a third-party vendor.",
                    "AWS Marketplace eliminates the need to upgrade to newer software versions.",
                    "Users can deploy third-party software without testing."
                ],
                "answer": "Users pay for software by the hour or month depending on licensing."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What is the value of using third-party software from AWS Marketplace instead of installing third-party software on Amazon EC2?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Marketplace enables the user to launch applications with 1-Click.",
                    "AWS Marketplace data encryption is managed by a third-party vendor.",
                    "AWS Marketplace eliminates the need to upgrade to newer software versions.",
                    "Users can deploy third-party software without testing."
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Marketplace enables the user to launch applications with 1-Click."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following is a cloud architectural design principle?",
                "choices": [
                    "Scale up, not out.",
                    "Loosely couple components.",
                    "Build monolithic systems.",
                    "Use commercial database software."
                ],
                "answer": "Loosely couple components."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Under the shared responsibility model; which of the following areas are the customer's responsibility?",
                "choices": [
                    "Firmware upgrades of network infrastructure",
                    "Patching of operating systems",
                    "Patching of the underlying hypervisor",
                    "Physical security of data centers"
                ],
                "answer": "Patching of operating systems"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Under the shared responsibility model; which of the following areas are the customer's responsibility?",
                "choices": [
                    "Firmware upgrades of network infrastructure",
                    "Configuration of the security group",
                    "Patching of the underlying hypervisor",
                    "Physical security of data centers"
                ],
                "answer": "Configuration of the security group"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which service enables customers to audit and monitor changes in AWS resources?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor",
                    "Amazon GuardDuty",
                    "Amazon Inspector",
                    "AWS Config"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Config"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service identifies security groups that allow unrestricted access to a user's AWS resources?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS CloudTrail",
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor",
                    "Amazon CloudWatch",
                    "Amazon Inspector"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Trusted Advisor"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "According to the AWS shared responsibility model, who is responsible for configuration management?",
                "choices": [
                    "It is solely the responsibility of the customer.",
                    "It is solely the responsibility of AWS.",
                    "It is shared between AWS and the customer.",
                    "It is not part of the AWS shared responsibility model."
                ],
                "answer": "It is shared between AWS and the customer."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service is a content delivery network that securely delivers data, video, and applications to users globally with low latency and high speeds?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS CloudFormation",
                    "AWS Direct Connect",
                    "Amazon CloudFront",
                    "Amazon Pinpoint"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon CloudFront"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which benefit of the AWS Cloud supports matching the supply of resources with changing workload demands?",
                "choices": [
                    "Security",
                    "Reliability",
                    "Elasticity",
                    "High availability"
                ],
                "answer": "Elasticity"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "A user is running an application on AWS and notices that one or more AWS-owned IP addresses is involved in a distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack. Who should the user contact FIRST about this situation?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Premium Support",
                    "AWS Technical Account Manager",
                    "AWS Solutions Architect",
                    "AWS Abuse team"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Abuse team"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are benefits of hosting infrastructure in the AWS Cloud?",
                "choices": [
                    "There are no upfront commitments.",
                    "AWS manages all security in the cloud.",
                    "Users have access to free and unlimited storage.",
                    "Users have control over the physical infrastructure."
                ],
                "answer": "There are no upfront commitments."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are benefits of hosting infrastructure in the AWS Cloud?",
                "choices": [
                    "Users have the ability to provision resources on demand.",
                    "AWS manages all security in the cloud.",
                    "Users have access to free and unlimited storage.",
                    "Users have control over the physical infrastructure."
                ],
                "answer": "Users have the ability to provision resources on demand."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What AWS service would be used to centrally manage AWS access policies across multiple accounts?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Service Catalog",
                    "AWS Config",
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor",
                    "AWS Organizations"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Organizations"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What is AWS Trusted Advisor?",
                "choices": [
                    "It is an AWS staff member who provides recommendations and best practices on how to use AWS.",
                    "It is a network of AWS partners who provide recommendations and best practices on how to use AWS.",
                    "It is an online tool with a set of automated checks that provides recommendations on cost optimization, performance, and security.",
                    "It is another name for AWS Technical Account Managers who provide recommendations on cost optimization, performance, and security."
                ],
                "answer": "It is an online tool with a set of automated checks that provides recommendations on cost optimization, performance, and security."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service or feature allows a company to visualize, understand, and manage AWS costs and usage over time?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Budgets",
                    "AWS Cost Explorer",
                    "AWS Organizations",
                    "Consolidated billing"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Cost Explorer"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS service offers on-demand access to AWS security and compliance reports?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS CloudTrail",
                    "AWS Artifact",
                    "AWS Health",
                    "Amazon CloudWatch"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Artifact"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services can host a Microsoft SQL Server database?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon EC2",
                    "Amazon Redshift",
                    "Amazon Aurora",
                    "Amazon S3"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon EC2"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services can host a Microsoft SQL Server database?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)",
                    "Amazon Redshift",
                    "Amazon Aurora",
                    "Amazon S3"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS characteristics make AWS cost effective for a workload with dynamic user demand?",
                "choices": [
                    "High availability",
                    "Shared security model",
                    "Elasticity",
                    "Reliability"
                ],
                "answer": "Elasticity"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS characteristics make AWS cost effective for a workload with dynamic user demand?",
                "choices": [
                    "High availability",
                    "Shared security model",
                    "Pay-as-you-go pricing",
                    "Reliability"
                ],
                "answer": "Pay-as-you-go pricing"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are characteristics of Amazon S3?",
                "choices": [
                    "A global file system",
                    "An object store",
                    "A local file store",
                    "A network file system"
                ],
                "answer": "An object store"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are characteristics of Amazon S3?",
                "choices": [
                    "A global file system",
                    "A durable storage system",
                    "A local file store",
                    "A network file system"
                ],
                "answer": "A durable storage system"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which services can be used across hybrid AWS Cloud architectures?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Route 53",
                    "Classic Load Balancer",
                    "Auto Scaling",
                    "Amazon CloudWatch default metrics"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Route 53"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which services can be used across hybrid AWS Cloud architectures?",
                "choices": [
                    "Virtual Private Gateway",
                    "Classic Load Balancer",
                    "Auto Scaling",
                    "Amazon CloudWatch default metrics"
                ],
                "answer": "Virtual Private Gateway"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS tools assist with estimating costs?",
                "choices": [
                    "Detailed billing report",
                    "Cost allocation tags",
                    "Cost Estimator",
                    "AWS Cost Predictor"
                ],
                "answer": "Cost allocation tags"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS tools assist with estimating costs?",
                "choices": [
                    "Detailed billing report",
                    "AWS Simple Monthly Calculator",
                    "Cost Estimator",
                    "AWS Cost Predictor"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Simple Monthly Calculator"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS tools assist with estimating costs?",
                "choices": [
                    "Detailed billing report",
                    "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator",
                    "Cost Estimator",
                    "AWS Cost Predictor"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "AWS supports which of the following methods to add security to Identity and Access Management (IAM) users?",
                "choices": [
                    "Implementing Amazon Rekognition",
                    "Using AWS Shield-protected resources",
                    "Blocking access with Security Groups",
                    "Using Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)"
                ],
                "answer": "Using Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "AWS supports which of the following methods to add security to Identity and Access Management (IAM) users?",
                "choices": [
                    "Implementing Amazon Rekognition",
                    "Using AWS Shield-protected resources",
                    "Blocking access with Security Groups",
                    "Enforcing password strength and expiration"
                ],
                "answer": "Enforcing password strength and expiration"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services should be used for read/write of constantly changing data?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Glacier",
                    "Amazon RDS",
                    "AWS Snowball",
                    "Amazon EFS"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon RDS"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services should be used for read/write of constantly changing data?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Glacier",
                    "Amazon Redshift",
                    "AWS Snowball",
                    "Amazon EFS"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Redshift"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are features of Amazon CloudWatch Logs?",
                "choices": [
                    "Summaries by Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)",
                    "Free Amazon Elasticsearch Service analytics",
                    "Provided at no charge",
                    "Real-time monitoring"
                ],
                "answer": "Real-time monitoring"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are features of Amazon CloudWatch Logs?",
                "choices": [
                    "Summaries by Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)",
                    "Free Amazon Elasticsearch Service analytics",
                    "Provided at no charge",
                    "Adjustable retention"
                ],
                "answer": "Adjustable retention"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are valid ways for a customer to interact with AWS services?",
                "choices": [
                    "Command line interface",
                    "On-premises",
                    "Software-as-a-service",
                    "Hybrid"
                ],
                "answer": "Command line interface"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are valid ways for a customer to interact with AWS services?",
                "choices": [
                    "Software Development Kits",
                    "On-premises",
                    "Software-as-a-service",
                    "Hybrid"
                ],
                "answer": "Software Development Kits"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following AWS services can be used to serve large amounts of online video content with the lowest possible latency?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Storage Gateway",
                    "Amazon S3",
                    "Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)",
                    "Amazon Glacier"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon S3"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following AWS services can be used to serve large amounts of online video content with the lowest possible latency?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Storage Gateway",
                    "Amazon CloudFront",
                    "Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)",
                    "Amazon Glacier"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazom CloudFront"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following security-related services does AWS offer?",
                "choices": [
                    "Multi-factor authentication physical tokens",
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor security checks",
                    "Automated penetration testing",
                    "Amazon S3 copyrighted content detection"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Trusted Advisor security checks"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following security-related services does AWS offer?",
                "choices": [
                    "Multi-factor authentication physical tokens",
                    "Data encryption",
                    "Automated penetration testing",
                    "Amazon S3 copyrighted content detection"
                ],
                "answer": "Data encryption"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are categories of AWS Trusted Advisor?",
                "choices": [
                    "Fault Tolerance",
                    "Instance Usage",
                    "Infrastructure",
                    "Storage Capacity"
                ],
                "answer": "Fault Tolerance"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following are categories of AWS Trusted Advisor?",
                "choices": [
                    "Performance",
                    "Instance Usage",
                    "Infrastructure",
                    "Storage Capacity"
                ],
                "answer": "Performance"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following services could be used to deploy an application to servers running on-premises?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
                    "AWS OpsWorks",
                    "AWS Batch",
                    "AWS X-Ray"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS OpsWorks"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following services could be used to deploy an application to servers running on-premises?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
                    "AWS CodeDeploy",
                    "AWS Batch",
                    "AWS X-Ray"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS CodeDeploy"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which design principles for cloud architecture are recommended when re-architecting a large monolithic application?",
                "choices": [
                    "Use manual monitoring.",
                    "Use fixed servers.",
                    "Implement loose coupling.",
                    "Rely on individual components."
                ],
                "answer": "Implement loose coupling."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which design principles for cloud architecture are recommended when re-architecting a large monolithic application?",
                "choices": [
                    "Use manual monitoring.",
                    "Use fixed servers.",
                    "Design for scalability.",
                    "Rely on individual components."
                ],
                "answer": "Design for scalability."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which design principles for cloud architecture are recommended when re-architecting a large monolithic application?",
                "choices": [
                    "Use manual monitoring.",
                    "Use fixed servers.",
                    "Design for scalability.",
                    "Rely on individual components."
                ],
                "answer": "Design for scalability."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services are defined as global instead of regional?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon Route 53",
                    "Amazon EC2",
                    "Amazon S3",
                    "Amazon DynamoDB"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon Route 53"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services are defined as global instead of regional?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon CloudFront",
                    "Amazon EC2",
                    "Amazon S3",
                    "Amazon DynamoDB"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon CloudFront"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "The financial benefits of using AWS are:",
                "choices": [
                    "reduced Total Cost of Ownership (TCO).",
                    "increased capital expenditure (capex).",
                    "deferred payment plans for startups.",
                    "business credit lines for stratups."
                ],
                "answer": "reduced Total Cost of Ownership (TCO)."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "The financial benefits of using AWS are:",
                "choices": [
                    "reduced operational expenditure (opex).",
                    "increased capital expenditure (capex).",
                    "deferred payment plans for startups.",
                    "business credit lines for stratups."
                ],
                "answer": "reduced operational expenditure (opex)."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following can an AWS customer use to launch a new Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) cluster?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Concierge",
                    "AWS CloudFormation",
                    "Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3)",
                    "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS CloudFormation"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following can an AWS customer use to launch a new Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) cluster?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Concierge",
                    "AWS Management Console",
                    "Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3)",
                    "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Management Console"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following security measures protect access to an AWS account?",
                "choices": [
                    "Enable AWS CloudTrail.",
                    "Grant least privilege access to IAM users.",
                    "Create one IAM user and share with many developers and users.",
                    "Enable Amazon CloudFront."
                ],
                "answer": "Grant least privilege access to IAM users."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following security measures protect access to an AWS account?",
                "choices": [
                    "Enable AWS CloudTrail.",
                    "Activate multi-factor authentication (MFA) for privileged users.",
                    "Create one IAM user and share with many developers and users.",
                    "Enable Amazon CloudFront."
                ],
                "answer": "Activate multi-factor authentication (MFA) for privileged users."
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which options does AWS make available for customers who want to learn about security in the cloud in an instructor-led setting?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor",
                    "AWS Online Tech Talks",
                    "AWS Blog",
                    "AWS Forums"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Online Tech Talks"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which options does AWS make available for customers who want to learn about security in the cloud in an instructor-led setting?",
                "choices": [
                    "AWS Trusted Advisor",
                    "AWS Classroom Training",
                    "AWS Blog",
                    "AWS Forums"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS Classroom Training"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following features can be configured through the Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) Dashboard?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon CloudFront distributions",
                    "Amazon Route 53",
                    "Security Groups",
                    "Elastic Load Balancing"
                ],
                "answer": "Security Groups"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following features can be configured through the Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) Dashboard?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon CloudFront distributions",
                    "Amazon Route 53",
                    "Subnets",
                    "Elastic Load Balancing"
                ],
                "answer": "Subnets"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services can be used to gather information about AWS account activity?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon CloudFront",
                    "AWS Cloud9",
                    "AWS CloudTrail",
                    "AWS CloudHSM"
                ],
                "answer": "AWS CloudTrail"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which AWS services can be used to gather information about AWS account activity?",
                "choices": [
                    "Amazon CloudFront",
                    "AWS Cloud9",
                    "Amazon CloudWatch",
                    "AWS CloudHSM"
                ],
                "answer": "Amazon CloudWatch"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following common IT tasks can AWS cover to free up company IT resources?",
                "choices": [
                    "Patching databases software",
                    "Testing application releases",
                    "Creating database schema",
                    "Running penetration tests"
                ],
                "answer": "Patching databases software"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "Which of the following common IT tasks can AWS cover to free up company IT resources?",
                "choices": [
                    "Backing up databases",
                    "Testing application releases",
                    "Creating database schema",
                    "Running penetration tests"
                ],
                "answer": "Backing up databases"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What can AWS edge locations be used for?",
                "choices": [
                    "Hosting applications",
                    "Delivering content closer to users",
                    "Running NoSQL database caching services",
                    "Sending notification messages to end users"
                ],
                "answer": "Delivering content closer to users"
            }
        },
        {
            "card": {
                "question": "What can AWS edge locations be used for?",
                "choices": [
                    "Hosting applications",
                    "Reducing traffic on the server by caching responses",
                    "Running NoSQL database caching services",
                    "Sending notification messages to end users"
                ],
                "answer": "Reducing traffic on the server by caching responses"
            }
        }
    ]
}